<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-03-28T15:45:33-05:00</updated><id>https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/feed.xml</id><title type="html">fastpages</title><subtitle>An easy to use blogging platform with support for Jupyter Notebooks.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">College Board Score4</title><link href="https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/CollegeBoardGrading4/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="College Board Score4" /><published>2023-03-28T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-03-28T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/cptplan</id><author><name></name></author><category term="College Board Grading" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reporting Category Scoring Criteria Comments Student Score Program Purpose and Function Input Program Functionality Output Main goal in the program Functionality demonstrated in video Input and output shown in the video Input will be the username and password and output is to save data in the database and show in API. 1/1 Data Abstraction Two code segments - one that shows how data has been stored in this list (or other collection type) - one that shows the data in this same list being used as part of fulfilling the program’s purpose Name of the variables representing the list being used in response what the data contained in this list is representing in the program Has a code segment that shows the arithmetic that calculates the triangle ratios. Shows a list. Has name of variables and describes the data in the list. 1/1 Managing Complexity a program code segment that shows a list being used to manage complexity in the program How list manages complexity by explaining why the list have to written or what code will change without lists I think my code is pretty complex because it connects 5 different code. The list will be pulling data from database 1/1 Procedural Abstraction Two program code segment - One provident that shows at least one effect parameter in the procedure - one showing about calling of student’s procedure Has code segment showing the student-developed procedure and has parameter and shows where the SDP is being called. Finally describes the functionality of the program well. 1/1 Algorithm Implementation Sequencing Selection Iteration Describes what identified procedure is and how it contributes to overall functionality I have sequencing for all the code and iteration for running APi and selection for the login thing in my personal site. 1/1 Testing Describes two calls that pass different argument and cause different result Conditions tested by each call result of each call Two different values that one is correct login and another is incorrect login is putting in the login site The conditions will be username and password is correct. Right username and password will be go to main page and wrong will be go different page. 1/1]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">College Board MCQ 3</title><link href="https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/mcq3/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="College Board MCQ 3" /><published>2023-03-27T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-03-27T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/quizcorr</id><author><name></name></author><category term="Museum" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Title</title><link href="https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/2023/03/27/model.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Title" /><published>2023-03-27T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-03-27T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/2023/03/27/model</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Unit 2.4b Using Programs with Data, SQL</title><link href="https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/2023/03/16/AP-unit2-4b.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unit 2.4b Using Programs with Data, SQL" /><published>2023-03-16T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-03-16T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/2023/03/16/AP-unit2-4b</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using Programs with Data is focused on SQL and database actions. Part B focuses on learning SQL commands, connections, and curses using an Imperative programming style,]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/images/python.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/images/python.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Unit 2.4a Using Programs with Data, SQLAlchemy</title><link href="https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/2023/03/13/AP-unit2-4a.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unit 2.4a Using Programs with Data, SQLAlchemy" /><published>2023-03-13T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-03-13T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/2023/03/13/AP-unit2-4a</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using Programs with Data is focused on SQL and database actions. Part A focuses on SQLAlchemy and an OOP programming style,]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/images/python.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/images/python.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>