<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-01-23T02:57:18-06:00</updated><id>https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/feed.xml</id><title type="html">fastpages</title><subtitle>An easy to use blogging platform with support for Jupyter Notebooks.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">College Board Score3</title><link href="https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/CollegeBoardGrading3/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="College Board Score3" /><published>2023-01-23T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-23T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/Grading3</id><author><name></name></author><category term="College Board Grading" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reporting Category Scoring Criteria Comments Student Score College Board Score Program Purpose and Function Input Program Functionality Output Main goal in the program Functionality demonstrated in video Input and output shown in the video Program has both an input and output. It describes it’s purpose as finding information about a triangle and its function as showing the triangle ratios of a triangle that has been inputted. 1/1 0/1 Data Abstraction Two code segments - one that shows how data has been stored in this list (or other collection type) - one that shows the data in this same list being used as part of fulfilling the program’s purpose Name of the variables representing the list being used in response what the data contained in this list is representing in the program Has a code segment that shows the arithmetic that calculates the triangle ratios. Shows a list. Has name of variables and describes the data in the list. 1/1 1/1 Managing Complexity a program code segment that shows a list being used to manage complexity in the program How list manages complexity by explaining why the list have to written or what code will change without lists Has code segment shoring the complexity but doesn’t explain it. They just gave another piece of code. 0/1 0/1 Procedural Abstraction Two program code segment - One provident that shows at least one effect parameter in the procedure - one showing about calling of student’s procedure Has code segment showing the student-developed procedure and has parameter and shows where the SDP is being called. Finally describes the functionality of the program well. 1/1 1/1 Algorithm Implementation Sequencing Selection Iteration Describes what identified procedure is and how it contributes to overall functionality Has sequencing, selection but no iteration or explanation. 0/1 0/1 Testing Describes two calls that pass different argument and cause different result Conditions tested by each call result of each call Doesn’t have two calls to the selected procedure only has noe. It does describe the condition and identify the result however. 0/1 0/1]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Title</title><link href="https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/2023/01/22/model.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Title" /><published>2023-01-22T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-22T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/2023/01/22/model</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">College Board Score2</title><link href="https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/CollegeBoardGrading2/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="College Board Score2" /><published>2023-01-16T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-16T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/Grading2</id><author><name></name></author><category term="College Board Grading" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reporting Category Scoring Criteria Comments Student Score College Board Score Program Purpose and Function Input Program Functionality Output Main goal in the program Functionality demonstrated in video Input and output shown in the video I think the purpose and input are clear, but how it works is not clear. You should write more about this 0/1 0/1 Data Abstraction Two code segments - one that shows how data has been stored in this list (or other collection type) - one that shows the data in this same list being used as part of fulfilling the program’s purpose Name of the variables representing the list being used in response what the data contained in this list is representing in the program I see the names or variables that the student represents. However, I cannot see the code that the student has to show 0/1 0/1 Managing Complexity a program code segment that shows a list being used to manage complexity in the program How list manages complexity by explaining why the list have to written or what code will change without lists It shows the list about animals and its picture. The student describes about the list and what happens while not using list. 1/1 0/1 Procedural Abstraction Two program code segment - One provident that shows at least one effect parameter in the procedure - one showing about calling of student’s procedure The Program has a parameter and it affects the functionality but doesn’t have a code segment showing this parameter or describe it. 0/1 0/1 Algorithm Implementation Sequencing Selection Iteration Describes what identified procedure is and how it contributes to overall functionality I saw selection and iteration on this code, but one is missing. I cannot see sequencing in this code. Also, the students didn’t explain about functionality 0/1 0/1 Testing Describes two calls that pass different argument and cause different result Conditions tested by each call result of each call Fist call is about correct answer and second one is about wrong answer. There is two conditions which is required. Lastly, it tells the results about first call and second call 1/1 1/1]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">College Board Score</title><link href="https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/CollegeBoardGrading/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="College Board Score" /><published>2023-01-08T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-08T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/Grading</id><author><name></name></author><category term="College Board Grading" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reporting Category Scoring Criteria Comments Student Score College Board Score Program Purpose and Function Input Program Functionality Output Main goal in the program Functionality demonstrated in video Input and output shown in the video Input and Output are clear. When the person enter three input, the degree of triangle with three inputs and table of sin, cos, tanz will be come out. However, the purpose is not that long. I want this student to write more specific. It would be better when this student writes why he makes or what he want to get. 0/1 0/1 Data Abstraction Two code segments - one that shows how data has been stored in this list (or other collection type) - one that shows the data in this same list being used as part of fulfilling the program’s purpose Name of the variables representing the list being used in response what the data contained in this list is representing in the program Two code segments are shown. One is for the list and other is for how to use the list in procedure. This student defines the list well and explain how the list uses by giving the example in those codes. 1/1 1/1 Managing Complexity a program code segment that shows a list being used to manage complexity in the program How list manages complexity by explaining why the list have to written or what code will change without lists The code segment that contains list is not included in this response. There is a word about why the list makes more complicate. 0/1 0/1 Procedural Abstraction Two program code segment - One provident that shows at least one effect parameter in the procedure - one showing about calling of student’s procedure This student shows the code with three parameter and explains about the function called ratioCalculate. Besides, he shows full code so that it can make teacher to understand easily. 1/1 1/1 Algorithm Implementation Sequencing Selection Iteration Describes what identified procedure is and how it contributes to overall functionality This student uses the word conditionals, so I can see that student utilizes the selection. And there is order because A, B, and C have to be inputted. This student also portrays the steps very easily to comprehend, so person like me can also read this. 1/1 1/1 Testing Describes two calls that pass different argument and cause different result Conditions tested by each call result of each call Results of each call are indicated and Conditions too. Inside the conditions, there are parameters too. At last, this students also expresses two calls which are ratioCalculate(3.0, 4.0, 5.0) and ratioCalculate(1.2, 2.3, 3.4) and have different arguments. 1/1 1/1]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Grades</title><link href="https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/grades/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Grades" /><published>2022-12-15T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2022-12-15T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://jw95z.github.io/JeongWooLee/grades</id><author><name></name></author><category term="Grades_from_Lessons" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Section grades Lesson comments hacks 3.1 ~ 3.2 0.8/1.0 Lesson I didn’t know the date to submit , so I got late. 3.1-3.2 3.3 ~ 3.4 0.9/1.0 Lesson I just only do what I supposed to do. I didn’t add details 3.3-3.4 3.8 and 3.10 2.0/2.0 Lesson I do my hacks creatively so that I can get a perfect score 3.8and3.10 3.9 and 3.11 0.95/1.0 Lesson My hacks were perfect, but the clear button on calculator did not work. Later, I knew that I didn’t put my function in clear button 3.9and3.11 3.12 ~ 3.13 0.99/1.0 Lesson I did all of my hacks, but I forgot that there is an extra thing and I did not do that. Therefore, I lost 0.01 points 3.12-3.13 3.14 ~ 3.15 0.95/1.0 Lesson I completed my all hacks, but I have to put detailed notes 3.14-3.15 3.16 1.0/1.0 Lesson I completed my all hacks. 3.16 3.17~3.18 0.93/1.0 Lesson I am not sure why I got 0.93 in this subject 3.17-3.18]]></summary></entry></feed>